



Senior software developer

55/118 Aispire Sathorn-Taksin (Timber Zone), Bang Kho, Chom Thong, Bangkok 10150

Tel.(+66) 880-923-074, e-mail: sornbuen15@gmail.com

Summary

My name is Jakkawan Rakharuthai. Born in July 10th, 1983. I'm experience in programming solutions that focus on PHP, Angular, Node.js, C#, Java, relational database. Front-end web development using PHP or CakePHP2.x, typescript languages and C# application or Java appliets for interactive functionality and back-end development using PHP, and a little bit experience front-end web development using Angular and Node.js

Work experience

JenniferSoft(Thailand) June 2019 – Present

Senior Software Developer (Full-stack Developer) using angular, NodeJS, Java, Kotlin.

I-WIZ TECH Feb 2018 – June 2019

Programmer (outsource) at AIS New Payment Team, Using angular, Nodejs, Java and Oracle.

Freelance Feb 2018 – Present

Website https://ripleysthailand.com Database Design, coding and implementation.

Netbay.Co.,Ltd. Feb 2018 – July 2018

Senior Software Developer

- Design and coding Angular front-end web application as a requirement from sale department.
- Design and coding PHP back-end application as a requirement from sale department
- Design solution to improve and urgent problem from customer services team.

Zicure.Co.,Ltd. May 2015 – Feb 2018

Senior Software Developer

 Get requirements from sale team with project manager and system analysis to make the design and software specifications.

- Create the tasks from software specifications and separate the tasks to small task for software developer team.
- Estimate timeline from small tasks with project manager, software developer team and tester team.
- Lead the software developer team to make all of the tasks as an according of the software specification based on estimated timeline
- Research and development new technology for support software developer team.
- Design and coding C# application to make private browser for open e-document web application. It could be connect between web application and Microsoft word to create an online document.
- Design and coding Front-end web application and Back-end application using CakePHP framework.
- Create Mog-up using pencil and Adobe XD Design for pre-sale.

Sycapt.Co.,Ltd. Feb 2010 – Oct 2015

Programmer

- Design and coding web application to helpdesk department, Inventory department and EDC technical department for support customers, Using PHP, Javascript, JQuery and Oracle.
- Design and coding web application for customers to request service about EDC machine, Using PHP,
 Javascript, JQuery and Oracle.

Education

Bangkok University, Bangkok, Thailand

Jun 2007 - Aug 2010

Bachelor of Engineering - Computer Engineering, GPA2.71

Wat Nuannoradit School, Bangkok, Thailand

Jun 2000 - Mar 2002

High school, GPA1.97

Skills

PHP ********

Web application using PHP or CakePHP Framework

C# *******

C# .Net Framework Application

Java *******

Java Application

Typescript ********

Angular, Node.js, Ionic

Database *******

Oracle, MS Access, MySql, MS-SQL and Postgresql

Tools *******

Docker, XMPP Openfire, eclipse, Netbean, VS Code, Visual Studio

Microsoft Office Suite: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Adobe Photoshop,

XD Design, Pencil

Hobbies

- Learn new technical for coding by myself
- Review my older coding
- Fencing
- Photographer
- Karaoke

Other Experience

- 1998 Present: Fencing athlete, type epee.
- 2003 2004: Keep and clean trolley at airport.
- 2004 2006: Barista at Coffee World, Khao san road Branch.
- 2008 2010: President of Bangkok University Fencing Club and captain team men epee.

References

- Mr. Vorrarit Lueangwattanakij, Technical Director, Zicure.Co.,Ltd(Pakgon Group), Bangkok, Thailand,
 vorrarit@pakgon.com
- Mr. Nayos Rajanon, Chief Executive Officer, Enchantec Company Limited, Bangkok, Thailand, nayos.ra@enchantec.com